Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
<This is Recon Ship 13.>
<Yamato sighted.>
<Repeat...>
<Enemies overhead!>
<Incoming!>
<Permission to launch.>
Anabiosis Performed Successfully
<Initiating connection.>
<You are skilled.>
<However...>
<This is the end.>
<Rear Brigadier Ghetto!>
<The Balgrey has been sunk! >
<What?!>
<Damn!>
<Ghale Domel!>
<Reverse.>
<Connected.>
Episode 20
Under a Rainbow Sun
Among the distant stars
Can you hear the wandering souls?
In this galaxy, they can forever rest in peace
Requiem of separation
With this requiem
Sing Along!
Voices sing to praise
An unforgettable memory
And we’ll never forget your name
Farewell friend,
my sorrow
Will not run out
Someday in this sea of stars
Surely
Pray for the Earth!
The oath
Pray for the dream!
The ideal
Last forever!